{"data":[{"question":"She can type very well, ______ she?","a":"can","b":"couldn't","c":"doesn't","d":"can't","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Tag question structure: \n+ Positive statement, negative tag? \n+ Negative statement, positive tag? \n+ If a modal (can, could, will, should, etc.) is used in the statement, then the same modal is used in the tag part","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"70","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"She didn't come with you, _______ she?","a":"didn't","b":"did","c":"has","d":"comes","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Tag question structure: \n+ Positive statement, negative tag? \n+ Negative statement, positive tag? \n- The verb in the statement should be the same tense as the verb in the tag \n- If the verb used in the statement is an auxiliary verb, then the verb used in the tag must match it","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"70","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"He doesn't come every day, ______ he?","a":"has","b":"does","c":"do","d":"is","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Tag question structure: \n+ Positive statement, negative tag? \n+ Negative statement, positive tag? \n- The verb in the statement should be the same tense as the verb in the tag \n- If the verb used in the statement is an auxiliary verb, then the verb used in the tag must match it ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"70","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"She wasn't very old, ______ she?","a":"was","b":"wasn't","c":"is","d":"does","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Tag question structure: \n+ Positive statement, negative tag? \n+ Negative statement, positive tag? \n- The verb in the statement should be the same tense as the verb in the tag \n- If the verb used in the statement is an auxiliary verb, then the verb used in the tag must match it ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"70","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"______ is your little brother?","a":"How many years","b":"How old","c":"What years","d":"How years old","answer":"2","explain":"\n- We use \" how old\" to ask about the age of someone","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"70","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"You aren't very tall, ______ you?","a":"aren't","b":"are","c":"do","d":"have","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Tag question structure: \n+ Positive statement, negative tag? \n+ Negative statement, positive tag? \n- The verb in the statement should be the same tense as the verb in the tag \n- If the verb used in the statement is an auxiliary verb, then the verb used in the tag must match it ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"70","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"You have been there before, ______ you?","a":"don't","b":"haven't","c":"have","d":"aren't","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Tag question structure: \n+ Positive statement, negative tag? \n+ Negative statement, positive tag? \n- The verb in the statement should be the same tense as the verb in the tag \n- If the verb used in the statement is an auxiliary verb, then the verb used in the tag must match it","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"70","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"You don't like onions, ______ you?","a":"do","b":"did","c":"like","d":"are","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Tag question structure: \n+ Positive statement, negative tag? \n+ Negative statement, positive tag? \n- The verb in the statement should be the same tense as the verb in the tag \n- If the verb used in the statement is an auxiliary verb, then the verb used in the tag must match it","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"70","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"She had an accident at _______ five.","a":"the years of","b":"years old","c":"the age of","d":"age of","answer":"3","explain":"\n- We use \" at the age of + number\" to mention the particular year-old","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"70","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"_______.","a":"He is 20 years.","b":"He is 20 years old.","c":"He has 20 years.","d":"He has 20 years old.","answer":"2","explain":"\n- S + to be + number of year old","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"70","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"}]}